Guide to the ACTWU's Executive Vice-President's Office Records
ACTWU's Executive Vice-President's Office Records
- Israel Bond Dinner/DuChessi: Reservations and Bond Orders, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  October 23
- Israel Bond Dinner/DuChessi: Sponsoring Committee Letter to and Replies, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  Letter to October 23; Replies August
- Israel Bond Dinner/DuChessi: Arrangements Committee Agenda and Program, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Israel Bond Dinner/DuChessi: Program, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Israel Bond Dinner/DuChessi: Supplies, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- U.S. International Trade Commission Hearings on Classifying Textile Imports, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  Washington D.C.; May/June
- Demonstration Re Foreign Imports, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  April 6
- Trade Negotiations General-Misc. and International Trade Comm. [Folder 1 of 2], 1975 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Trade Negotiations General- Misc. and International Trade Comm. [Folder 2 of 2], 1975 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Import: Petition of ACTWU for Countervailing Duties on Textile Mill Products and Men's and Boys' Apparel, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- The Impact of Imports on the Men's Clothing Industry, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Federal Trade Commission: Textile Industry Mergers Policy, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- ACTWU Education Departments, 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- ACTWU Engineering Division [Folder 1 of 2], 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- ACTWU Engineering Division [Folder 2 of 2], 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Dyers Meeting, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  February 14; 99 University Place
- Dyers Industry, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Dyers: Passaic Valley Sewerage Division, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Dyers: GHI, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Dyers Leaders: re GHI, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  November 9; Local 1733 in Paterson, NJ
- Finance Department: Textile Division Expenditures [Folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Finance Department: Textile Division Expenditures [Folder 2 of 2], 1979 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Dyers Division Meeting, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  August 1 in NYC
- ACTWU Engineering Department, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- ACTWU Finance [Folder 1 of 2], 1981 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- ACTWU Finance [Folder 2 of 2], 1981 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- ACTWU: Murray Finley Memorandum, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Murray H. Finley, 1976-1981 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- ACTWU Finance, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- ACTWU Finance Department [Folder 1 of 2], 1980 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- ACTWU Finance Department [Folder 2 of 2], 1980 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- ACLU Dinner Honoring Roger Baldwin, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  June 13; NYC
- Pins & Needles: ILG, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Humphrey-Hawkings Testimonial Dinner:Workers Defense League Anniversary, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  June 8; Hotel Roosevelt, NY
- Dyers Conference: F. Cuccio, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  June 7
- Debs/Thomas Dinner in Honor of National Women's Political Caucus, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  June 6; Hotel Roosevelt
- Friends of Leopold Sedar Senghor: President of Republic of Senegal, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  June 6; NYC
- AFL-CIO International Affairs Committee for Gen Pyotr Grigorenkb, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  June 5; NYC
- Black Trade Unionist Dinner, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  June 3; NYC
- Invitations: General, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Ralph Bunche Memorial Dinner, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  May 24; American Hotel
- Hillman Foundation Prize Award Lunch, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  May 5; Biltmore, NYC
- Urban League Dinner, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  May 4; Americana, NYC
- AFL-CIO Civil Rights Conference, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  April 16-20; Washington D.C.
- Social Democrats-Debs Award, L. McBride Honoree, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  April 17; Hotel Roosevelt, NYC
- ACTWU COPE-Legislative Institute, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  April 13-14; Washington D.C.
- Histradrut Luncheon for Gregory J. Bardacke, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  April 14; NY Hilton
- Testimonial Dinner Honoring Leo Perlis, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  March 30; Hotel Pierre NYC
- 11th Human Rights Award Dinner Honoring Martin Ward, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  March 29; NYC
- Consumer Assembly Awards Dinner, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  March 23; Statler-Hilton
- ACTWU Testimonial Dinner Dance, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  March 18; In honor of Kilmer Caban and Sydney Bykofsky; Hilton, NYC
- Boy Scouts of America Lunch Honoring Gerry Waters, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  March 9
- Histadrut Labor Council Luncheon, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  March 1; 33 E. 67th St.
- William Stern Testimonial Lunch, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  by National Comm. For Labor Israel; February 26; Plaza Hotel, NYC
- American T.U. Council for Histadrut Humanitarian Award to Sol Chaikin, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  January 24
- Jewish Labor Committee Administrative Committee, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  January 9
- A.H. Raskin Award Luncheon: Institute of Collective Bargaining, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  January 17; 49 E. 68th St., NYC
- ACTWU Christmas & Chanukah Party, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  Shirt Joint Board; December 23; 111 E. 15th St., NYC
- Invitations: Miscellaneous [Folder 1 of 3], 1977 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  January to December
- Invitations: Miscellaneous [Folder 2 of 3], 1977 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Invitations: Miscellaneous [Folder 3 of 3], 1977 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- National Conference for Christians & Jews: Ted Kheel Dinner, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  June 19; Plaza Hotel
- Zonarich Dinner, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  December 19; Holiday Inn, Ft. Mill, SC
- Amos Eran Meeting, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  December 1; Plaza Hotel, NY
- Glenn E. Watts Dinner, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  November 21, NYC
- American Friends of the Hebrew U. Dinner for Dr. Irving J. Selikoff, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  November 10; Americana Hotel, NYC
- Chicago Trade Union Council for Histradrut Dinner for Sol Brandzel, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  November 6; Chicago
- A. Philip Randolph Award Dinner-Dance Honoring Sammy Davis Jr., 1977 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  October 28
- Israel Labor Award to Lillian Roberts, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  October 26
- Italian American Trade Union Council Luncheon, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  November 12; Statler-Hilton, NY
- Brotherhood Award Lunch for B.G. Cox and Burt Ruby, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  October 10, NYC
- Testimonial Dinner in Honor of Jacob Sheinkman, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  October 16; Workmen's Circle Home, Bronx, NY
- Testimonial Dinner Honoring Vincent Ricciardella, ACTWU V.P., 1977 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  October 1; Waldorf Astoria, NYC
- Luncheon for Emanuel Muravchik, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  October 7; New York, NY
- Professionals for Histadrut Dinner Honoring Stephen C. Vladeck, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  Labor Attorney; Sol Stetin Sponsor; September 25, Plaza Hotel NYC
- U.N. We Believe-Ambassadors Dinner, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  September 23; Waldorf-Astoria, NYC
- I.W. Abel Reception and Dinner, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  September 15; Shoreham-Americana, Washington D.C.
- Passaic County Democratic Committee, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  September 16; West Paterson, NJ
- LID Honoring Al Barkan, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  June 4
- B'nai B'rith Dinner for Henry Segal, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  June 11; Americana Hotel, NYC
- Workers Defense League Honoring Jacob Sheinkman, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  June 8; Sol Stetin Sponsor
- New York Labor Forum, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  June 8; 351 Broadway, NYC
- DSOC Dinner Honoring Martin Gerber, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  June 2; Statler-Hilton, NYC
- United Steelworkers Installation of International Officers and Dedication, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  June 1; Dawson, PA
- Catholic Interracial Council of NY, Inc. Award to Terence Cardinal Cooke, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  May 26, NY
- Bob Roe for Governor, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  May 22
- National ALS Foundation Inc., 1977 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  May 22; World Trade Center, NYC
- Sidney Hillman Foundation Luncheon, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  May 10; Biltmore Hotel, NYC
- Reception for Mario Soares Prime Minister of Portugal and General Secretary of the Socialist Party of Portugal, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  April 22; Hotel Roosevelt, NYC
- Tribute to David J. Fitzmaurice, President of IUE, AFL-CIO, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  April 27; Washington D.C.
- Suburban Action: Dinner Honoring Osborn Elliott and Lewis Rudin, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  April 22; NYC
- B'nai B'rith Award Honoring Si Cohen, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  April 16; Hilton, NYC
- Social Democrats U.S.A. Tribute to George Meany, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  March 31
- National Committee for Full Employment, Honoring Hubert Humphrey, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 63)
  March 16; Washington D.C.
- Passaic County AFL-CIO Labor Council Dinner-Dance Honoring Julien De Meyer and Oakley Evans, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 64)
  February 11
- Boy Scouts of America/Men & Boys Wear Lunch-O-Ree, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  January 27; Waldorf-Astoria, NYC
- Tribute to Toots Shor, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  January 27
- Labor Forum Luncheon, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  January 19, NYC
- Tenth Labor Human Rights Award Dinner to Sol C. Chaikin and ILGWU, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  January 12; Waldorf-Astoria, NYC
- Histadrut Testimonial Dinner Honoring Harry Golden and Harold McIver, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  January 8; Royal Villa Motor Inn, Raleigh, NC
- Conference: Governor's Task Force and NY State School of Industrial and Labor Relations of Cornell University, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  November; Statler-Hilton Hotel, Buffalo, NY
- Invitations: General, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 71)
- Luncheon with Dr. Herbert Ehrenberg, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  September 15; NYC
- NJ Americans for Democratic Action, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  September 20; West Orange, NJ
- Meeting with Henry Weinberger, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 74)
- New England Organizing, 1976-1982 (Box 10, Folder 75)
- New England Clippings, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  From Denis Blais; English and Spanish
- New England Wage Negotiations, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 77)
- Data for Re New England Wage Negotiations, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 78)
- New England Contract Expirations: Textile Division, 1979-1982 (Box 10, Folder 79)
- New England: Central Massachusetts Joint Board, 1976-1981 (Box 10, Folder 80)
- New England: Southern New England Joint Board, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 81)
- New England: Southern New England Joint Board Minutes, 1978-1981 (Box 10, Folder 82)
- Staff Retirement: Miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- New England: Southern New England Joint Board, 1978-1981 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  Rhode Island Office has been included in Southern N.E. Joint Board
- New England: Greater Fall River Joint Board By-Laws, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- New England: Southern New England Joint Board Memorandum, 1978-1981 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  Merged with Southern New England Joint Board May 1982
- Granite State and Northeastern Massachusetts Joint Boards Coordinated Conference, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  October 15-17
- New England: Granite State Joint Board, 1976-1982 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Northeastern Joint Board Proposed Merger of Locals, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- New England: Northeastern Massachusetts Joint Board, 1978-1981 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- New England: Staff Meeting, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  June 19; Providence, RI; Re: Maine Joint Board
- New England: Maine Joint Board, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Biddeford-Saco Joint Board and Lewiston Joint Board Merger Talks, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- New England Matters, 1977-1982 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Southern New England Joint Board, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  Willimantic, Connecticut
- Maine: General Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Maine Joint Board [Folder 1 of 2], 1978-1981 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Maine Joint Board [Folder 2 of 2], 1978-1981 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- New York State Personnel, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Meeting of New York State Managers: Textile Division, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  October 23, NYC
- New York State Organizing, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Buffalo Joint Board: Honoring John Harrison and R. Slisz, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  June 17
- Buffalo Joint Board: Requests for Staff, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Buffalo Regional Textile Joint Board Correspondences, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- New York State: Greater New York Joint Board, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- New York State: Hudson Valley Joint Board, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Harry Wilson Dinner: Central and South Jersey Joint Board, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  November 4; Piscataway, NJ
- Dyers Meeting: Local 1733, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  March 7; Paterson, NJ
- ACTWU Dyers Local 1733, 1979-1981 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  Some Newspaper Clippings
- Local 1733: Special Mailings, 1979-1982 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  Paterson, NJ
- Quin State: Local 2052, 1975-1981 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  Union City, NJ
- Quin State: Personnel, 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Quin State News, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  First Issue: December 1981
- Quin State: Staff, 1979-1983 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Joseph Coponi, Regional Director: General, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Quin State: Organizing, 1978-1981 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Garden Spot Joint Board: Robert Hinkle: Manager, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Quin State: Delaware Valley Joint Board, 1979-1982 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Delaware Valley Joint Board Annual Party, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  February 7; Stewartsville, NJ
- Quin State: Garden Spot and Schuylkill Valley Joint Boards, 1976-1983 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Local 2010: Finances, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  Reading, PA
- Pennsylvania Keystone Joint Board, 1978-1982 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Pennsylvania Keystone Joint Board Conference, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  June 10-12; Tamiment, PA
- Pennsylvania Keystone Joint Board Annual Party, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  November 6; Christy Joy's, Pottsville, PA
- Pennsylvania Keystone Joint Board Annual Picnic, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  September 14; Bushkill, PA
- Quin State: Pennsylvania Keystone Area Keenagers Spring Ball, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  May 2; Montgomeryville, PA
- Quin State: Jack Coury, Pennsylvania Keystone Joint Board, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Quin State: Philadelphia Joint Board, 1976-1982 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Local 6, 1976-1981 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  Lewistown, PA
- Quin State: Local 630, 1973-1979 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  New Brunswick, NJ
- Quin State: Local 148-T, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 49)
- Local 944-T, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  Wall Rope Works Inc.
- Local 1034, 1978-1982 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  Huntingdon, PA
- Bi-Annual Banquet: Local 1369, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  November 18; Collegeville, PA
- Quin State: Local 1762, 1976-1980 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  Works out of office of Local 6
- Quin State: Local 1859, 1977-1980 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  Phillips Fibers; Hanover, PA
- Quin State & N.Y. Staff Conference, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  September 7-9; Mt. Pocono, PA
- Ohio State Educational Conference, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  April 27-29; Medina, OH
- Quin State Conference, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  January 4, 1979; Summit Hotel, NYC
- Howard D. Samuel, 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  Vice President
- Key Votes, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Economy Articles [Folder 1 of 2], 1975 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Economy Articles [Folder 2 of 2], 1975 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Legislative, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Legislative [Folder 1 of 2], 1975 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Legislative [Folder 2 of 2], 1975 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Voting Record in Congress of Richard C. White, 1967-1975 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Voting Records, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  Issued by other unions
- Voting Records: 90th and 91st Congress, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Endorsement Issue: Advance, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Executive Council Reports, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- AFL-CIO Conference Meeting of George Meany, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Defense Fund: Weekly Report, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Meetings, Receptions, and Affairs During Democratic National Convention, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Dues Increase, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- National Union of Tailors and Garment Workers General Conference [Folder 1 of 2], 1977 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  Scarborough, Great Britain
- National Union of Tailors and Garment Workers General Conference [Folder 2 of 2], 1977 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Dyers Division Meeting, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  June 16, 1975
- Dyers & Printers Division, 1976-1979 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- TWUA Dyers Vacation & Welfare Fund, Dyers Life Insurance Fund, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  William Gordon
- Miscellaneous: Ethics, Energy and Employment, 1973-1979 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Education Department, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Elections Information [Folder 1 of 2], 1977 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Elections Information [Folder 2 of 2], 1977 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Miscellaneous: Fair Labor, 1973-1979 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- FBI: Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- ACTWU Per Capita Payments, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Miscellaneous: Government, General, Group Research, 1974-1978 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Alfred Goldis, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Jack Goldstein, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Giltspur Exposystems, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Miscellaneous: Health Education, Health Care, and Human Rights, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- The Heritage Foundation, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  "Metric" Report
- Histadrut, 1976-1979 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- International Chemical Workers Union, 1969-1976 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Histadrut Dinner: Sol Stetin, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  May 1, 1976
- Miscellaneous: International, Inaugural and ILO News, 1971-1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Industrial Engineering Department [Folder 1 of 2], 1976-1979 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  John Weiser, Director
- Industrial Engineering Department [Folder 2 of 2], 1976-1979 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, AFL-CIO, CLC, 1974-1978 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- International Textile Garment and Leather Workers Federation [Folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- International Textile Garment and Leather Workers Federation [Folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- International Trade Commission, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Investments: Securities, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Israel Embassy, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Israel Conflict, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Italian American Labor Council, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- InterAmerican Textile, Leather and Garments Workers Federation (FITITVC), 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- International Association of Machinists & Aerospace Workers, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU), 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- "IF": International Foundation of Employee Benefit Plans [Folder 1 of 2], 1976-1979 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- "IF": International Foundation of Employee Benefit Plans [Folder 2 of 2], 1976-1979 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Congressional District Committee Kit, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- AFL-CIO: West Penn Power Company Newspaper Clippings, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- ACTWU: PAC, APEC, PEF, SPAF Mailed Contributions, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- APEC & SPAF Made Contributions [Folder 1 of 2], 1976 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- APEC & SPAF Made Contributions [Folder 2 o f2], 1976 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Invitations [Folder 1 of 4], 1978 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Invitations [Folder 2 of 4], 1978 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Invitations [Folder 3 of 4], 1978 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Invitations [Folder 4 of 4], 1978 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Contributions [Folder 1 of 2], 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Contributions [Folder 2 of 2], 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Congressmen Contributions, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Congressmen Contributions, Events and Invites, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Appeals From Candidates And For Political Affairs [Folder 1 of 2], 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Appeals From Candidates And For Political Affairs [Folder 2 of 2], 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- International Textile Garment and Leather Workers Federation [Folder 1 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- International Textile Garment and Leather Workers Federation [Folder 2 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Contributions to Candidates [Folder 1 of 3], 1972-1977 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Contributions to Candidates [Folder 2 of 3], 1972-1977 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Contributions to Candidates [Folder 3 of 3], 1972-1977 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Communications On Behalf Of Candidates [Folder 1 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Communications On Behalf Of Candidates [Folder 2 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous ACTWU Documents, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- ACTWU Legislative and Political Education Institute, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Invitations: Political [Folder 1 of 2], 1976 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Invitations: Political [Folder 2 of 2], 1976 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Address Index Cards [Folder 1 of 3] (Box 15, Folder 9)
  Photocopies
- Address Index Cards [Folder 2 of 3] (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Address Index Cards [Folder 3 of 3] (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous Documents and Newsletters, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Various Memos, Newsletters and Contributions [Folder 1 of 3], 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Various Memos, Newsletters and Contributions [Folder 2 of 3], 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Various Memos, Newsletters and Contributions [Folder 3 of 3], 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- ACTWU Synthetics Division Training Institute [Folder 1 of 2], 1977 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- ACTWU Synthetics Division Training Institute [Folder 2 of 2], 1977 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Political Newsletters, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Labor Union Articles: North Carolina, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Receipts, Lists and Essays, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Industrial Union Department-Essex Committee Meeting, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  February 13
- ACTWU Inter-Office Memorandum, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- SALT II: A Soft Bargain, A Hard Sell, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Reports on Attitudes and Opinions of Union Members and Other Residents on Issues and Candidates, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  Texas and Colorado
- Special Report for Textile Workers Pension Fun, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  From the Pension Fund Department
- 1978 Review of the World Economic Situation (Box 16, Folder 10)
- William DuChessi: Memorandum, Contributions and Articles, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Literature [Folder 1 of 4], 1978 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Literature [Folder 2 of 4], 1978 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Literature [Folder 3 of 4], 1978 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Literature [Folder 4 of 4], 1978 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Health Insurance Program, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Textile Workers Union of America: Canadian Employees Retirement Trust Fund, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Staff Retirement Plan Report, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Correspondence: Financial Statements, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  William C. Tutt; July 1-December 1, 1977
- Strike Assistance Program (Box 16, Folder 20)
- GEB Reports [Folder 1 of 3], 1978 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- GEB Reports [Folder 2 of 3], 1978 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- GEB Reports [Folder 3 of 3], 1978 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- ACTWU Resolutions, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- William DuChessi. Correspondence [Folder 1 of 6], 1978 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- William DuChessi. Correspondence [Folder 2 of 6], 1978 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- William DuChessi. Correspondence [Folder 3 of 6], 1978 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- William DuChessi. Correspondence [Folder 4 of 6], 1978 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  Includes Photographs
- William DuChessi. Correspondence [Folder 5 of 6], 1978 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- William DuChessi. Correspondence [Folder 6 of 6], 1978 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- ACTWU Political Action Committee Receipts, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  Blank Contribution Receipts, Numbers 116031-116140 discarded